Cereal killer.
玉米片殺人狂 （音同連續殺人狂）
Cereal killer?
玉米片殺人狂？
Hey,come on,I say more dumb things before 9 a.m...
我一早說的蠢話
...than most people say all day.
比別人整天說的還多
What?
怎麼了？
I can't find anything that I wanna eat. Everything makes me nauseous.
我不知道要吃什麼 吃什麼都會噁心
I'm telling you,being pregnant is no piece of cake. Oh,cake!
懷孕有夠難搞的…啊，蛋糕
No.
不行
Honey,I'm sorry.
真可憐
What is that smell? It's coming from the bathroom.
什麼香味？是浴室傳出來的
Pregnancy does give you some weird cravings.
你倒是多了些怪癖
It's me. It's Phoebe. Listen,there's something in here I want to eat.
是我，菲比 這裡有我想吃的東西
What smells so good?
什麼味道這麼香？
-ls it the shampoo? It's guava. -No.
是新洗髮精嗎？番石榴香味 不是
Wait.
等一下
Is it my bologna sandwich?
是我的紅腸三明治嗎？
Yes. Yes. Yes.
對，沒錯
I can't believe it. The baby wants bologna. The baby wants meat. I can't eat meat.
寶寶居然想吃紅腸 寶寶想吃肉，我不能吃肉
Wait!
等一下
Maybe it's the pickle!
也許是醃黃瓜
The One With the Fake Party
本集播出：「求愛十八招」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
（中央咖啡館）
What are you writing?
你在寫什麼？
Joshua's coming in tomorrow,and since I don't have the guts to ask him out...
約書亞明天要來 既然我沒膽約他
...I'm gonna sell him a coat and put this note in the pocket.
我決定賣他一件外套 再把紙條塞進口袋
"Joshua,give me a call sometime. Guys like you...
「約書亞：有空打電話給我」 「你這樣的人…」
...never go out of style."
「…永不退流行」
What did you throw away?
你扔了哪些人？
-Hi,guys. -What have you guys been up to?
你們做了什麼？
We went to see a collection of Victorian doorknobs at the museum.
我們去看維多利亞時期門把展
Without me?
沒找我去？
My uncle dragged us there, but it turned out to be really interesting.
是舅舅拖我們去的 結果很有意思
They were so ornate and beautiful. Look at that.
那些門把很華麗，你們看
I don't know how museums work in England, but here,you're not supposed to take stuff.
我不知道英國的國情 但這裡不能順手牽羊
I got it from the gift shop.
這是禮品部的
They have really lax security there.
那裡沒什麼防盜措施
It's a joke.
這是笑話
Anyone for more tea?
（英國腔）誰還要喝茶？
No,just me then.
（英國腔）那我自己叫了
Hey,Ringo.
鸚鵡先生
Every time Emily's around,you talk like her. Would you please cut it out?
每次艾蜜莉在，你就怪腔怪調 別鬧了
I think you like it.
我看你喜歡喔
I think you can't resist me when I do it.
你無法抗拒這樣的我
You want to eat me up like a cream "pumpy."
你想一口…了我
-What? -All right,look,I don't know all the words.
什麼？ 我不是每個英國字都會
Right. I've got to be off. I'll see you. Bye-bye,then.
我該走了，再見咯
Bye-bye,then.
再見咯
You guys seem to be having a good time.
你們相處得很愉快
She is amazing, and she's so much fun.
對，她人很棒，而且很有趣
And you know what? When I'm with her,I'm fun!
跟她在一起時，我也很有趣
I do things like run off to Vermont...
我會跑去佛蒙特
...and you guys saw the doorknob.
你們也看到那個門把了
I even signed up for helicopter classes.
我甚至報名學開直升機
She's leaving in two days. I don't have to do it.
她過兩天就走了，我不必真學
Two days? You must be bummed.
兩天？你一定很失望
She's got to go back to London,but I've been prepared for this from the start.
她非回去不可 不過我早就有心理準備
We both knew we had two weeks together, and then that's it.
我們都知道我們只有這2星期
Hey,that's what all my relationships are like.
我的每段戀情都是
Yes,but in Ross' case, they both know in two weeks that's it.
羅斯他們是「雙方」都知道 只有2星期
-Pheebs! -Hello. Hello.
菲比
No,I know. Yeah.
寶寶好啊 好啦
So the baby is totally craving meat.
寶寶想肉想瘋了
I tried tricking it,and I made it a soy burger, so that maybe it'd think it was getting meat.
下午我想用素肉堡騙他 讓他以為他吃到肉
And I got nauseous.
結果就反胃了
Maybe that's because soy burgers suck.
也許是因為素肉堡粉難吃
But I'm no obstetrician....
不過應該很營養
Being pregnant is hard on your tummy.
懷孕真難吃東西
At least you got that cool,pregnant-lady glow.
但你有一種孕婦的光彩
That's sweat. You throw up all morning, you'll have that glow too.
你要是吐一早上也會有光彩
Okay.
-Here's that trench coat that you wanted. -Great.
這是你要的風衣 太好了
It's comfortable.
很舒服
You could really flash somebody in this.
這可以用來裝變態
No. They don't want you to put your hands in the pockets until you are out of the store.
不行，出了店門 才能把手放進口袋裡
Why not?
為什麼？
Well,because...
因為…
...we get a lot of
有很多人…
They ruin it for everybody.
真是害群之馬
I know.
是啊
I wore that sweater on a date last night.
我昨晚穿那件 喀什米爾毛衣去約會
It was the first date since the divorce.
我離婚後第一次約會
Congratulations. So do you love her?
恭喜，你愛她嗎？
She's nice, but it made me realize...
她還不錯，不過我也發現
...I'm just not ready to be dating.
我還沒有心情約會
That's interesting.
真有意思
-What was that? -Just an anti-theft device.
那是什麼？ 只是防盜磁條
Then what's this?
那這是什麼？
You need that too,because a thief could just tear this up.
那個也要，因為這個一撕就碎
We have to have a party in five minutes, so everybody cancel your plans.
晚上有派對 其實是5分鐘後，有事快取消
What's going on?
你在說什麼？ 怎麼回事？
We have to have a bon-voyage party for Emily.
我們要幫艾蜜莉辦驚喜歡送會
But it's actually for Joshua.
其實是為了約書亞
That sucks. Nobody's ever thrown me a bon-voyage-Emily party.
討厭 都沒人幫我辦過假歡送會
He said he's not ready to date.
他說他還沒有心情約會
So I had to invite him to a party if I wanted to see him outside of work.
我得找他參加派對 才能在工作之外見到他
And now I have created the perfect opportunity to seduce him.
現在我製造了一個 色誘他的完美機會
As much as I'd like to meet Josh and warn him...
我很想當面警告約書亞
...Emily and I won't be here. She's gonna come by to say goodbye...
但艾蜜莉和我不能參加 她會來說聲再見
...and then I've got a special evening planned. Sorry. No party.
然後我安排了整晚的節目 對不起，沒戲唱了
-Hello? -Surprise!
驚喜！
Surprise!
No one's thrown me a surprise party before.
沒有人替我辦過驚喜派對
Well,it was all Ross' idea.
這都是羅斯的主意
You're so sweet.
你真好
And I'm so surprised.
我好驚喜喔
You didn't know?
你真的沒料到？
Why are you over here if Joshua's over there?
約書亞在那邊，你怎麼在這邊
I'm trying to play hard-to-get.
我想假裝很難上手
Quick! He's looking. Say something funny.
快，說句好笑的話
Like what?
舉個例？
What's so funny?
什麼事這麼好笑？
I said,"Like what?"
我說「舉個例」
Now that's a thinker.
真深奧
This playing-hard-to-get thing is not working.
假裝很難上手沒用
Hand me those cherries.
把櫻桃給我，好…
-Care for a cherry? -No,thanks.
要吃櫻桃嗎？ 不要，謝謝
I can tie one of these into a knot using just my tongue.
我可以用舌頭把櫻桃梗打結
You okay?
你還好嗎？
You all right?
沒事吧？
We should probably get going soon.
我們得趕快走了
But the party's just getting started.
但是派對才剛開始
We have to be at The Four Seasons for drinks in 15 minutes.
我們得在15分鐘內 趕去四季餐廳喝酒
Then The Plaza for dinner.
然後去廣場飯店吃晚飯
So why did you plan a party at the same time?
那你為什麼還辦派對？
不是的
Actually,American surprise parties are very short.
其實美國的驚喜派對都很短
It's usually,"Surprise!" Then,"My God,I'm so surprised. Bye!"
通常都「驚喜！」 然後就「我好驚喜喔！再見」
Ross,I'm having such a great time.
但是我覺得好好玩
Your sister told me that you used to dress up like old ladies...
你妹說你以前會扮成老太太
...and host make-believe tea parties.
舉辦假的茶會
Monica said that,did she?
摩妮卡說的是吧？
Did she tell you that when she was little...
她有沒有說她小的時候
...she was partially responsible for new legislation...
遊樂器材商增加鞦韆的載重量
...regulating the strength of swing sets?
她也是原因之一？
Then what are you going to put on top of that?
你接下來要放什麼？
-A little salami. -Oh,yeah.
一點蒜味肉腸 贊
What goes on top of the salami?
蒜味肉腸上面呢？
Pastrami.
熏牛肉 太讚了
You're a genius.
你真是天才
Give me a hand with the zipper.
幫我拉一下拉鏈
Up!
往上拉
-You changed? -I decided I needed my lucky dress.
你換衣服？ 對，我需要我的幸運裙
-Lucky means more cleavage? -lt does for me.
幸運是指露更多乳溝？ 我覺得是
Look at him! He's so cute.
你們看他多帥
I just want to grab him and kiss him.
真想一把捉過來親下去
How could I kiss him without him knowing I like him?
但是他不知道我喜歡他
I know how you can get him. Take off your bra.
有個辦法-脫胸罩
What?
什麼？
-This scene in Footloose -Flashdance.
在「渾身是勁」裡… 是「閃舞」
-Yeah. With that plumber girl? -A welder.
對…那個水電女工 是焊接工
Were you,like,in the movie?
你是有演嗎？
She takes off her bra under the shirt and pulls it out the sleeve.
總之她在衣服底下脫掉胸罩 從袖子抽出來
Very sexy. And classy.
非常性感，而且有格調
-Or you could use mistletoe. -It's not Christmas.
不然你也可以用檞寄生 又不是聖誕節
-Spin-the-bottle. -He's not 11.
轉瓶子 他不是小孩子
Thank you so much for this. It was so thoughtful of you.
謝謝你們，你們真用心
You're leaving?
你們要走了？
-We have something we have to get to. -I'm gonna take off too.
對，我們還有事 我也要走了
You can't leave yet. You have to stay.
先別走，留下來
We've got the whole big thing planned.
我們準備了重頭戲
What big thing?
什麼重頭戲？
Spin-the-bottle works like this: I spin the bottle.
轉瓶子的規則是，我轉瓶子
Lands on Gunther, so I would have to kiss Gunther.
指向阿甘，我就要親阿甘
All right.
就這樣
Who wants to go first?
誰要先？
I'll go.
我先
Welcome to America.
歡迎來到美國
Oh,my God!
天哪
Two in a row! You gotta use your tongues now.
連續兩次！來個舌吻吧
All right.
再來
What are the odds?
太巧了
That's enough!
夠了
Let's let someone else play.
讓別人玩吧
If you didn't want to play, then why'd you come to the party?
你不想玩幹嘛來？
All right,I'll go.
我來好了
Somebody loose. Somebody loose.
豪放女！豪放女
Story of my life.
我的人生寫照
再轉一次
Story of my father's life.
我爸的人生寫照
Okay,my turn.
該我
Look at that!
是你！
Oh,my God.
天哪
The baby just kicked!
天哪，寶寶踢了
It's okay. It's okay. If it kicked once,it'll kick again!
他會再踢的
Everybody just remember where they were sitting.
大家要記住剛才的位置
It was a bug.
有蟲
It doesn't matter how much I'm craving it.
不管我多想吃
You know why I'm never gonna eat meat? Because it's cold-blooded murder.
我絕不吃肉，那是冷血謀殺
Okay.
好
There's a Phoebe on my sandwich!
我的三明治上有菲比
What are you doing?
菲比，你幹什麼？
I can't help it!
我沒辦法
I need the meat! The baby needs the meat.
我要吃肉，寶寶要吃肉
You know when you're dating someone...
跟別人交往...
...and you don't want to cheat unless it's with someone really hot?
...要專一 除非第三者真的很辣
Totally.
那當然
This is the same kind of deal.
這就對了
If you're gonna do something wrong...
吃肉也一樣，要錯…
...do it right.
就要錯得漂亮
-I'll be back in a minute. -Okay.
我馬上回來 好
What are you doing to me?
你想怎樣？
I'm trying to get Emily out of here, and you keep talking to her...
我想把她帶走 你卻一直跟她講話
...being all interesting and making her laugh.
裝風趣又逗她笑
I don't want you to be funny anymore.
從現在起，請你別那麼風趣
Rachel wants me to be funny, you don't want me to be funny.
瑞秋要我風趣 你卻不要我風趣
From now on,I'm gonna be funny sometimes,and not funny others.
從現在起，我要有時候風趣 有時候不風趣
You feel better now?
感覺好多了嗎？
Yeah,but at what cost?
對，但是代價呢？
Six more months,three meals a day.
三餐吃肉吃半年？
I am going to eat,like, you know,millions of cows.
我會吃掉 幾百萬頭牛
Mommy cows,daddy cows,baby cows
牛爸爸，牛媽媽，牛寶寶
No. No,I will never eat baby cows. No veal!
我絕不吃牛寶寶，死也不吃
Oh,but veal.
盡量不吃
What if I even things out for you,meat-wise?
要是我幫你平衡過來呢？ 什麼？
-What? -I eat a lot of meat,right?
我很會吃肉對吧？ 對
But suppose,until the baby's born, I laid off it.
要是在寶寶出生前，我戒吃肉
No extra animals would die. You'd be eating my animals.
就不會多死動物 你是在吃我的份
I can't believe you'd do that for me.
你居然願意為我這麼做
Absolutely. I could be a vegetarian.
當然願意，我也可以吃素
There's no meat in beer,right?
啤酒裡沒有肉吧？
We can still make dinner if we skip the appetizers and ask for our check right away.
不吃開胃菜，馬上買單 還趕得上吃主菜
We can't go now. Rachel is going to put on a skit.
現在不能走，瑞秋要表演
Oh,my God! Have you lost your mind?
我的天哪，你瘋了嗎？
I am finally thinking clearly.
不，我終於想通了
My lucky dress wasn't working out too well for me.
我的幸運裙效果不佳
But for four years, this baby never missed.
但這一套整整4年都百發百中
Wait,I can't let
瑞秋，我不能讓你…
Actually,I want to see what happens.
我也想看熱鬧
Nice costume.
好棒的行頭
Well,I wanted to give Emily a big American goodbye cheer.
是啊，我想給艾蜜莉 來個美式的再見歡呼
Ready. Okay.
預備…起
Give me an "E"!
給我一個E E
Give me an "M"!
給我一個M M
Give me an "I"!
給我一個I I
Give me an "L"!
給我一個L L
Give me a "Y"!
給我一個Y Y
What do you get?
加起來是什麼？
Emily! Emily!
艾蜜莉！艾蜜莉…
That's me as a cheerleader!
以上就是我的歡呼
I loosened a tooth. It's no big deal. I have a dentist.
有一顆牙齒鬆了 小意思，我有牙醫
I'll put some ice on it. Excuse me.
我去冰敷，失陪
-What do I do now? -I think you're done.
怎麼辦怎麼辦？ 你應該是毀了
Time to take off the bra.
該脫胸罩了
That was really great.
剛才的表演很精彩
But I gotta take off.
但是我得走了
Take the bra off.
脫~胸~罩
Let's go get your coat.
我陪你去拿外套
Rachel's my girlfriend.
瑞秋是我的女朋友
So this was really fun.
今晚蠻開心的
Yeah,it was real fun.
是啊，很開心
You know,this bra...
這件胸罩…
...is really bothering me.
實在很不舒服
This used to be my bedroom.
這裡以前是我的房間
A lot of memories in here. Lot of memories.
有很多回憶，很多很多回憶
If these walls could talk, they'd say:
要是牆壁會說話，它們會說
"Want to hear some memories?"
「想聽聽往事嗎？」
Need a hand?
你需要幫忙嗎？
I got this all under control.
不用，沒問題
You really don't seem like you do.
可是看起來不像
God! Forget it!
算了啦！真是…
This is not how this was supposed to happen.
事情不該是這樣的
What was supposed to happen?
不然應該怎樣？
Can you not look at me when I say this?
你能不能不要看我？
I thought that if I could get you here...
我以為要是能把你找來
...I could seduce you.
我就可以色誘你
-Excuse me? -Seduce you.
什麼？ 引誘你
I don't wear suits to work.
我上班不穿西裝
And I bought six of them from you.
卻跟你買了六套
I'm sorry. I thought you needed them.
抱歉喔，我以為你有需要
My point is,I kept coming back because I wanted to see you.
我一直去找你，因為我想見你
-Why? -Because I like you.
為什麼？ 因為我喜歡你
You like me?
你喜歡我？
I mean,you're beautiful and smart and sophisticated.
是啊，你漂亮、聰明又成熟
A lot of this isn't based on tonight.
這些印象不是來自今晚
But you like me?
但是你喜歡我？
I can't believe this. All this time, I liked you and you liked me!
這段日子以來 我們竟然一直互相喜歡
-But -No "but."
但是… 不要說「但是」
"But" is never good. Let's leave it at "l like you and you like me."
「但是」都沒好事 停在「我們互相喜歡」就好
-Okay. However -No,that's a fancy "but."
好，然而… 那是好聽的「但是」
My marriage,like,just ended.
我剛結束我的婚姻
And I'm really not ready to get into anything yet.
我還沒心情跟別人交往
But....
但是…？
I'm sorry. I just need a little time.
對不起，我需要一點時間
Okay.
There you are. I was looking for you.
你在這裡，我在找你
Joshua's gone, so you and Emily are free to go.
約書亞走了 你和艾蜜莉可以走了
It's okay.
無所謂
She's still in there enjoying her fake party.
她還在裡面享受這場假派對
It's too late to do the stuff I had planned.
現在要做什麼也來不及了
I'm sorry. I ruined your evening.
抱歉，我毀了你美好的夜晚
Yeah.
是啊
If it makes you feel any better, I made a fool of myself.
我出了個大醜 你有沒有高興一點？
Helps a little.
有一點
Is there room on that step for a pathetic loser?
有地方讓悲慘的失敗者坐嗎？
Have a seat.
坐吧
-I'm so sorry. -It's okay.
對不起 沒關係
It was just a two-week thing anyway.
反正只是一段2星期的戀情
I just didn't want it to end this way.
我只是不想這樣結束
Or maybe you didn't want it to end.
也許你不想結束呢？
What do you mean?
什麼意思？
You seem to really like her.
你似乎真的很喜歡她
I really do.
沒錯
But what am I going to do? We agreed it'd be a two-week thing.
但我能怎麼辦？ 我們說好只在一起2星期
No commitment.
不要有承諾
羅斯
That girl just spent the entire evening talking to your friends...
那個女孩整晚都跟你的朋友
...asking to hear stories about you...
吵著要聽你的事
...Iooking through Monica's photo albums.
還拿摩妮卡的相簿來看
You don't do that if you're just in it for two weeks.
只想在一起2周才不會這麼做
You think?
是嗎？
You've got 14 hours until she has to be at the airport.
她還有14個小時才要去機場
And you're sitting here in a hallway...
你卻坐在走廊上
...with a 28-year-old cheerleader with a fat lip.
陪一個28歲 嘴腫起來的啦啦隊長
You're right.
你說得對
Thanks.
謝了
What photo album was it?
哪一本相簿？
I don't know. It was you and a bunch of albino kids.
不知道 你跟一堆白子小孩的合照
Oh,my God! Those weren't albino kids.
他們不是白子
That was computer camp!
那是電腦夏令營啦
-You're a pathetic loser,right? -Oh,yeah.
你是悲慘的失敗者吧？ 就是我
Sit!
坐
Hi.
Oh,my God. Joshua.
天哪，約書亞
Look...
聽著...
...all those things I said about not being ready
...我剛才說我沒心情…
-They're not true? -They're all true.
不是真的？ 不，都是真的
But....
但是…
I love that "but."
我喜歡這個「但是」
Do you want to go inside and get some coffee?
要不要進去喝杯咖啡？
Okay.
好
Every time.
百發百中
-What do you got there? -Pastrami.
你放什麼？ 熏牛肉
贊
-You know what goes good with that? -Corned beef.
你知道什麼跟它最配？ 醃牛肉
I was going to say bologna. But that's better.
我想說紅腸，但醃牛肉更棒
-How about that smoked turkey? -Okay.
要不要放點熏火雞肉？ 好
Oh,mama!
媽呀
-When is the baby due? -Six months.
寶寶什麼時候生？ 半年後
If a cow died of natural causes, I could have one of those,right?
自然死亡的牛可以吃吧？
Not if I get there first.
我會先下手